https://www.auctr.edu/about/library-policies/privacy-policy-guidelines/

THE AUC WOODRUFF LIBRARY'S SERVICES AND RESOURCES ARE AVAILABLE ONLINE. TO VIEW AUC'S COVID-19 UPDATES, CLICK HERE.
About Our Library
Who is Robert Winship Woodruff?
AUC Robert W. Woodruff Library Privacy Policy
AUC Robert W. Woodruff Library (AUC RWWL) is committed to protecting your online privacy. The only information AUC RWWL obtains about individual visitors to this web site is information supplied voluntarily by the visitor. This policy outlines the practices of AUC RWWL regarding the collection and use of your personal information from your visit to our web site.
Personally Provided Information
In general, you can visit official AUC RWWL web sites without revealing any personal information. If you choose to provide us with any personal information by sending an email or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it through a AUC RWWL web site, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us provide you with information or material that you request. We do not give, share, sell or transfer any personal information to a third party unless required by law.
Email Communications
Email communication that you send to us via the email links on our sites may be shared with an employee or contractor that is most able to address your inquiry. We make every effort to respond in a timely fashion once communications are received.
Collection of Technical Information
AUC RWWL uses IP addresses (the Internet address of your computer) to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our site. For instance, we run statistical software to identify those parts of our site that are more heavily used and which portion of our audience comes from within the AUC RWWL network. But, we do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. While aggregate statistical reports may be generated based on site usage, no personally identifiableinformation will ever be disseminated to any unaffiliated third party.
Links to Other Sites
Please note that some pages within AUC RWWL web site, for the convenience of users, are linked to web sites not managed by the library. AUC RWWL does not review, control or take responsibility for the content of these web sites. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new web site.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may change the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions on the AUC RWWL web site. By accessing or using the AUC RWWL web site, you agree to be bound by all the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy as posted on the RWWL web site at the time of your access or use. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised statement, please exit the site immediately.
Complaint Process
If you have a complaint or problem, or if you believe your privacy rights have been violated, you may email us at webmaster@auctr.edu. Please indicate the reason for contacting us. Our Communications department will forward your complaint to the appropriate AUC RWWL entity for response or resolution.
Overview
About Our Library
Who is Robert Winship Woodruff?
